{
    "id": "d1c6b6b4e8d94368be8866cedae0bb1f",
    "title": "As vs. Like",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is as beautiful ………………………. an angel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The jewels shone ……………………….. stars.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... you know, I am looking for a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She talks …………………………. a scholar.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They were fighting …………………………….. dogs.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt ..................................... crying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. responsible citizens, we should abide by the rules and regulations.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks ……………………….. Princess Diana.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks ................................... it is starting to rain.",
            "description": "Like is possible here in an informal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "as if",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She talks .................................... she is rich.",
            "description": "As if is used to say how a particular situation seems like. ",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as if",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat there crying .................................... he had lost everything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as if",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She sings …………………………… a nightingale.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}